Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XX: Schools/Students/Teachers.
  - Bushwick HS Graduation Brooklyn - UFT Scholarship Awards (RKO Madison Theater), Jun 28, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13434)
  - PS 196 Vacation Day Camp Brooklyn, Aug 3, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13453)
  - Prospect Park Brooklyn Wolman skating rink Summer School of Program Arts, Aug 12, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13456)
  - Prospect Heights HS Brooklyn Federal School Summer Program Awards, Aug 12, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13455)
  - New York Hilton Haaren HS Mini School Luncheon [Haaren HS, located at 10th Ave between 58th and 59th streets, closed in the late 1970's.], Aug 17, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13457)
  - Childhood Center Abe Levine Brooklyn, Sep 14, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13475)
  - Hillcrest [classroom], Sep 27, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13490)
  - Ecology Program Mr. Schwartz, Sep 30, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13494)
  - Student Voter Registration J Richmond HS, Oct 1, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13495)
  - Mrs. Kimbel PS 76 LIC Queens, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13504)
  - HS Art & Design Parents/Teachers Meeting, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13508)
  - August Martin HS George Altomare, Oct 7, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13510)
  - IS 102 Bronx "Teacher of Year", Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13512)
  - Julia Richmond HS, Ivan Tiger, New Program, Oct 8, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13517)
  - IS 348 Brooklyn, broken into sub-school conference, Oct 13, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13524)
  - Haaren HS NYC Mini school John Hill, Oct 15, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13533)
  - Coop City School - Duffy, Oct 20, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13552)
  - Students of School of Art & Design with Pres. Isaiah E. Robinson, Board of Education, Oct 21, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13547)
  - PS 85 Astoria Street Blocking, Oct 22, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13560)
  - PS 45 Jamaica Early Childhood Preschool [Collection includes contact sheets for frame #s: 13561-1 through 13561-31.], Oct 22, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13561)
  - Demo - Boycott on Portable Schools PS 191 K Brooklyn, Oct 27, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13569)
  - JHS 275 Brooklyn Senator & Congressman [Unidentified Individuals], Oct 27, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13570)
  - George Altomare speaking to crowd 260 P.A.S., Oct 28, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13572)
  - Port Richmond HS Voter Registration Assembly, Oct 28, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13577)
  - Board of Education Portable Demonstration PS 191, Oct 29, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13576)
  - PS 98 Bronx Crotona Park Clean up, Oct 30, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13584)
  - Ivan Tiger & Justin Finger 260 PAS, Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13599)
  - PS 86 Queens Joan Agin, Nov 4, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13600)
  - HS Art & Design Albert Shanker Speaking to Students, Nov 5, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13597)
  - PS 11 Ivan Tiger With Chapter Chairmen & principal visiting classes, Nov 5, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13598)
  - HS of Art & Design Faculty Exhibit, Nov 15, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13627)
  - P[uerto] R[ican] Discovery Day Brooklyn PS 284 Brooklyn, Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13635)
  - PS 23 Bronx New Supt., Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13636)
  - JHS 136 Bronx District 12 Policemen [giving parents student reports], Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13637)
  - PS 60 Bronx P[uerto] R[ican] Program, Nov 18, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13638)
  - PS 47 Bronx Puerto Rican [Discovery Day and Vocational Schools Rally], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13648)
  - AL. F. Smith HS Brooklyn Carpentry Class, Paul Johnson [Alfred E. Smith HS, Bronx?], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13655)
  - IS 318 Food Exhibit Maureen Vidal, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13654)
  - PS 274 Brooklyn Puerto Rico Day, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13652)
  - Ft. Hamilton HS Brooklyn Carnaville 71, Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13656)
  - PS 114 Bronx Puerto Rican [Discovery Day and Vocational Schools Rally], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13648)
  - PS 274 Brooklyn chapter chair retiring Alan Luben [?], Nov 19, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13653)
  - Voter Registration Frank K Lane HS, George Altomare, Jim Bauman, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13664)
  - Anniversary of School PS 45 Brooklyn, Mrs. Orshaw, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13667)
  - PS 297 Brooklyn Puerto Rico Discovery Day, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13660)
  - Chapter Chairman Meeting JHS 143, Nov 23, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13662)
  - Forest Hill HS Queens Meeting of Students with Joan Agin about becoming teachers, Nov 23, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13661)
  - Thanksgiving Day Feast PS 188 Brooklyn, Marta Gross, Labell Harrison, Nov 24, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13666)
  - Primary Program PS 84 Brooklyn, Mr. Herman, Dec 1, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13682)
  - PS 190 Panel PTA, Dec 2, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13693)
  - Sickle Cell Anemia Program PS 332 Brooklyn, Murry Sussman, Dec 3, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13685)
  - International food festival Wingate HS Brooklyn, Stanley Finger, Dec 3, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13686)
  - Bayside HS Queens Play (rehearsal), Dec 7, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13707)
  - JHS 111 Brooklyn Gym Show, Dec 8, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13708)
  - PS 299 Award Winners at Black Expo, Dec 8, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13709)
  - PS 215 Brooklyn Dedication to Dr. Morris H. Weiss, Dec 9, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13719)
  - St. Johns Hospital PS 309, Dec 10, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13722)
  - PS 90 Queens Aero-Space Program, Dec 10, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13720)
  - PS 77 Bronx Open Classroom / Open House, Dec 15, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13735)
  - HS of Fashion & Industries, Shirley Chisholm, Dec 17, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13741)
  - IS 302 Dedication, Dec 17, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13745)
  - Planning Conference, Julia Richmond HS, Dec 20, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13750)
  - Peter & the Wolf HS for the Deaf, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13769)
  - PS 107 Christmas Carols, NY Stock Exchange, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13751)
  - Brooklyn school to Fiddler on the Roof, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13773)
  - Food & Maritime HS Manhattan, John Hall [Students cooking and adults (teachers?) taste-testing. There is a film crew visible in the shoot, filming the activities.], Dec 22, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13754)
  - PS 107 X'mas Carols, City Hall, Dec 22, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13764)
  - PS 168 Manhattan Folk Ballet, Mrs. Scivillo, Dec 23, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13767)
  - PS 219 Brooklyn X'mas Party, Dec 23, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13766)
  - Erasmus Hall HS X'mas concert, Brooklyn, Dec 23, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13765)
  - Choral Singers - PS 159 Bronx, front of "Wurlitzer Piano," Jerome Rochman, Dec 23, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13768)
  - PS 198 Manhattan [classroom], Jan 7, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13782)
  - PS 297 Brooklyn Play Music Man, Jan 7, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13779)
  - PS 274 Congressman Badillo (Brooklyn), Jan 7, 1972 (Box 25, Item 13780)
  - PS 304 Brooklyn Painters Picket line [Painters District Council 9 picketing], Jan 11, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13792)
  - PS 304 Brooklyn Kindergarten Reading Program, Jan 11, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13793)
  - Activities Day - George Washington HS, Jan 12, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13790)
  - PS 127 Queens Martin Luther King Day, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13799)
  - NY School of Printing Guidance Counselors Self-Help Program, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13800)
  - PS 179 Queens Velma Hill, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13801)
  - PS 307 Brooklyn "the American Dance Center", Jan 21, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13804)
  - PS 305 Brooklyn Ossie Davis & Classes, Jan 21, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13805)
  - Para-Professional Meeting IS 131 Bronx, Jan 24, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13809)
  - Demonstration PS15, Jan 26, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13811)
  - Rikers Island (women's) prison [school] [School began as PS 616; now known as PS 189.], Jan 26, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13812)
  - PS 155 Pre-school center, Jan 27, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13813)
  - Columbia University - Rikers Island Rehabilitation Center, Jan 28, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13817)
  - Sarah J Hale JHS Brooklyn Dedication, Teachers Lounge, Jan 28, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13818)
  - John Jay HS Brooklyn Comm. On Overcrowding, Teachers Lounge, Jan 28, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13819)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn & Annex overcrowding, Jan 31, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13822)
  - Mario Ranno - Gershow [?] PS 93, Feb 3, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13824)
  - PS 70 Queens Boycott, Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13823)
  - PS 102 Para-Professional Carol Landau [?], Feb 4, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13825)
  - JHS 232 Brooklyn - Program of Living Witness - Velma Hill, Feb 8, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13828)
  - Chinese New Year PS 23, Feb 10, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13829)
  - PS 302 Reading Clinic Rally, Feb 12, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13833)
  - JHS 162 Brooklyn rundown condition, Feb 15, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13840)
  - PS 244 K Brooklyn Americana USA, Feb 16, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13842)
  - Local School Board #1 PS 34, Feb 16, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13850)
  - Chinese New Year PS 2, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13851)
  - Afro American History PS 224 Brooklyn, Feb 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13852)
  - JHS 45 Manhattan Afro American History week, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13848)
  - PS 157, District 7, Brooklyn, Negro History Week, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13853)
  - PS 312 Brooklyn Peter Pan, Feb 22, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13862)
  - Stuyvesant HS Art Show, Feb 22, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13869)
  - PS 186 Manhattan Press Conference & School Damages, Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13866)
  - PS 257 Brooklyn Brotherhood Part [?] & Aw. [?], Feb 23, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13865)
  - PS 162 Bronx Mini School Classes, Feb 24, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13864)
  - PS 282 Negro History, Feb 25, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13863)
  - PS 136 Bronx [basketball team], Feb 28, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13879)
  - Teen Aid HS, Feb 28, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13876)
  - PS 148 Dedication, Mar 1, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13881)
  - PS 136 Science Fair, Mar 2, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13882)
  - Burnside Manor Annex & Open Classroom Bronx, Mar 7, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13883)
  - PS 303 Brooklyn Handicapped Children Project Search, Mar 7, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13887)
  - Singing group, Mar 11, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13891)
  - JHS 294 Brooklyn Science Fair, Mar 15, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13896)
  - PS 107 Manhattan - Closing, Mar 17, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13904)
  - Jamaica HS Willowbrook Clothing [Drive sponsored by] Avis, Mar 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13911)
  - Jane Addams JHS Bronx [singing], Mar 29, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13924)
  - IS 162 Bronx [classroom], Apr 13, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13935)
  - Boys HS Brooklyn - Swahili Classes, Apr 14, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13936)
  - PS 75 Brooklyn Pan-American Day & Fashion Show, Apr 14, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13939)
  - PS 20 Brooklyn Science Fair, Apr 17, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13945)
  - PS 171 Manhattan Boycott, Apr 18, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13946)
  - PS 35 Jamaica Experim[ental] Classroom, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13950)
  - PS 198 Manhattan Pan A[merican] Fiesta, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13951)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn Martin Luther King Statue, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13952)
  - Ridder HS Bronx Math lab, Apr 24, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13953)
  - PS 110 security meeting Bronx, Apr 24, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13954)
  - PS 31 Gold Jubilee, Apr 26, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13960)
  - JHS 198 Rockaway aerospace program, Apr 27, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13963)
  - PS 2 Pre-school center, May 2, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13971)
  - PS 119 Brooklyn Drug prevention program, May 2, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13972)
  - PS 43 Bronx, The Me Nobody Knows, May 9, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13979)
  - Kings Bridge Vol. Hospital - Francis Lewis HS, Bells are Ringing, May 10, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13988)
  - Fashion Show PS 144 Brooklyn, May 11, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13990)
  - A[ndrew] Jackson HS Queens, Drop out, May 12, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13994)
  - PS 130 Bronx Play, May 12, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13996)
  - PS 73 Bronx School Yard, May 12, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13995)
  - PS 40 Queens [teachers' meeting], May 15, 1972 (Box 29, Item 13998)
  - PS 26 Queens PTA Tea, May 15, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14000)
  - Sickle Cell [Blood Testing for students], PS 167 Brooklyn, May 17, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14012)
  - IS 10 Manhattan, Bro[c?]k Peters Auditorium, F[rederick] Douglas Day, May 19, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14013)
  - IS 145 Mini School Opening, May 19, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14014)
  - PS 221 Brooklyn, King & I, May 19, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14016)
  - Fair Art Exhibit PS 6 Manhattan, May 24, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14032)
  - PS 6 outdoor fair, May 24, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14027)
  - District 23 Brooklyn Musical programs, May 25, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14030)
  - Ben Franklin HS Art Exhibit, May 31, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14044)
  - PS 75 Brooklyn children's Caravan Purabeltre, Jun 1, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14039)
  - PS 83 Brooklyn Spec. Program, Jun 1, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14038)
  - PS 214 Brooklyn Dance Festival / Art Festival, Jun 5, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14043)
  - Sommers [?] JHS 252 International Festival, Jun 6, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14054)
  - Culture Fair PS 72 Bronx, Jun 7, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14055)
  - DeWitt Clinton HS Faculty/Student show Scholarship Fund, Jun 9, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14056)
  - PS 161 Bronx Awards Art, Jun 12, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14059)
  - Fordham University Panel [Jules Kolodny speaking], Jun 20, 1972 (Box 29, Item 14070)
  - PS 15 Gil Millstern, Apr 6, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14294)
  - JHS 271 Brooklyn Ponsie Hillman, Apr 12, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14305)
  - Brooklyn Basketball Roy Mann HS, Nov 17, 1977 (Box 30, Item 15586)
- Series XXI: Special Education.
  - Columbia University Retarded Children, Jun 6, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8425)
  - School for the Deaf, Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12230)
  - Picket line [for] Deaf [classrooms] at City Hall, Dec 11, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12273)
  - Board of Education PS 207 PS Retarded Children Sid Harris, Apr 21, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12529)
  - Board of Education Handicapped Awards Sid Harris, May 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12609)
  - Wheelchair [Baseball game], Sep 18, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12763)
  - School for Deaf, 23rd St & 2, 3, Ave. Traffic Light Demonstration, Oct 7, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12800)
  - School for the Deaf opening, Oct 20, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12825)
  - School for Deaf Art Exhibit, Jun 3, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13368)
  - Center for Handicapped Children, Jun 11, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13393)
  - CRMD [Children with Retarded Mental Development] Committee, Oct 18, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13540)
  - PTA Mrs. Aronow School for the Deaf, Oct 26, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13565)
  - Special Education Committee, George Washington Hotel, Nov 16, 1971 (Box 24, Item 13628)
  - Special Education Teachers, Dec 13, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13729)
  - Peter & the Wolf HS for the Deaf, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13769)
  - L I University Mayors Comm. [?] Hearing on Disabled, Jan 11, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13795)
  - New York University Hospital Hearing on Disabled, Jan 12, 1972 (Box 26, Item 13796)
  - PS 303 Brooklyn Handicapped Children Project Search, Mar 7, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13887)
  - Picket line Gov. Office, Handicapped, Mar 15, 1972 (Box 27, Item 13897)
  - Center for Multiple Handicapped, 106 Street, Apr 21, 1972 (Box 28, Item 13949)
  - Glen Cove Spec. Ed. Comm., Oct 19, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14460)
  - Spec. Ed. Comm. Albert Shanker, Oct 31, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14475)
- Series XXII: Strikes.
  - Teachers' Guild (strike), Apr 16, 1950 (Box 1, Item 119)
  - Teachers' Guild Strike at Board of Education, Sep 25, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4329)
  - Pre-strike rally [back of speakers' heads], Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Dave Selden addressing pre-strike rally, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Pre- strike rally - Placard-holders, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - St. Nic[hola]s Arena - exterior, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - United [Federation of] Teachers Strike at St. Nic[holas Arena], Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 5908)
  - Strike Captains' Meeting, Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - George Altomare addressing strike captains, Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - Strike Captains [Meeting], Mar 23, 1962 (Box 3, Item 7545)
  - Honor Picket Line PS 75 [Signs in English and Spanish; one reads "We go back at 8:30 today, but in September - all the way".], Mar 29, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7556)
  - Del[egate] Assembly Strike vote Roosevelt Aud[itorium], Jun 8, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7742)
  - Manhattan Center Strike vote membership & Greek Union Pres[ident?], Jun 14, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7770)
- Series XXIII: Training, Certification, and Workshops
  - Teachers' Guild Teacher's Class CCNY, Nov 7, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1482)
  - Cornell University Seminar, Sep 24, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9277)
  - Cornell Course [Charles] Cogen, Feb 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11674)
  - French Course, Mar 17, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11722)
  - Italian Course, Mar 18, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11723)
  - In Teaching, Sep 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12047)
  - Narcotics Clinic [Seems to be a training session; administrators from different schools and districts present.], Oct 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12122)
  - Teachers Training Class UFT H.Q., Feb 26, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12410)
  - Panels & Workshops, Exhibits, Mar 21, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12452)
  - Woodrow Wilson H.S. Drug Addiction [a narcotic addicts] Clinic, May 12, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12580)
  - PS 3 Brooklyn Narcotics Program & Lecture, Dec 9, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12949)
  - MES 102 Bronx People in Workshop, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13054)
  - Workshop on funded programs Brooklyn, Feb 9, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13065)
  - PS 271 Brooklyn Bi-Lingual workshop, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13068)
  - HS Design & Art Panel Discussion S[andy] Feldman, Mar 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13167)
  - IS 318 Teacher Training Institute - Brooklyn, Mar 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13169)
  - District 16 Auxiliary Training Center, May 3, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13260)
  - Course "History of Cooperative Movement" Exec. Bd. Rm., Oct 6, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13507)
  - HS Equivalency Course Hy Peck 260 P. A. S., Oct 19, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13543)
  - Course "Theory of Cooperatives" Executive Board Room, Oct 20, 1971 (Box 23, Item 13545)
- Series XXIV: Miscellaneous.
  - Cloth[ing Drive], Brooklyn, 0000-00-00 (Box 30, Item 15610)
  - Teachers' Guild [man getting on train], Feb 18, 1952 (Box 1, Item 639)
  - C[ogen, Charles?] K[olodny, Jules?] M[arch] of D[imes] School Flyer Program City Hall Mayor Wagner Silver Theobald, Nov 6, 1958 (Box 1, Item 4444)
  - [Hanging up] Paintings, Dec 29, 1962 (Box 2, Item 7328)
  - Bronx ["End School Violence" banner hanging on stage], Mar 19, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8198)
  - Merrill Lynch [Richard Greene giving a talk, presumably at Merrill Lynch; stock information behind him on bulletin board.], Mar 23, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8202)
  - Art Exhibit, May 1, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8291)
  - Car sign ["Effective Schools" bumper sticker], May 7, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8303)
  - Jamaican Visitors at UFT, Aug 12, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8480)
  - Freedom Mississippi Report, Oct 16, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8607)
  - Art Exhibit, Nov 6, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8640)
  - P. S. Art Exhibit at Lever House, May 17, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9027)
  - Art Exhibit, Nov 1, 1965 (Box 4, Item 9369)
  - School Children at Plant [School children tour plant or factory; and same group at lunch (hosted by plant?) in a conference room or boardroom.], Apr 14, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9815)
  - Clothing Drive Queens, May 27, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9941)
  - Irving Berger Receives Back Pay, Jul 8, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10015)
  - Hudson Drug [Three men talking over a Hudson Catalog, presumably discussing healthcare for the union.], Nov 10, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10130)
  - Career Exhibit [at] Kingsbridge Armory [UFT's "Teaching as a Career" booth pictured.], May 1, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10464)
  - 1st Bimonthly Checks PS 136, May 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10488)
  - Labor Art Exhibit Riverside Museum, May 20, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10502)
  - Kenya & [bags of] mail, Dec 21, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10980)
  - St. Michael's Freedom School, Sep 25, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11371)
  - Art Exhibit, Oct 4, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11392)
  - Board of Education, Computer "Dial A Drill" [With "Dial a Drill" students can telephone for automated math/science/etc drills to practice at home.], Mar 13, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11711)
  - Art Exhibition, May 9, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11844)
  - Block Party, May 24, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11896)
  - Ng. [?] Moertt [?] HS Auction, Jun 3, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11932)
  - Kemble 35mm, Sep 12, 1969 (Box 30, Item 15596)
  - Actors/Models for slides at Joseph Glenn[?] Childhood Care, Dec 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12121)
  - Attendance counselor Bureau, Dec 5, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12250)
  - Membership Card, Dec 10, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12289)
  - AFTU [?] Dinner [A formal dinner with a man named Herman Stein receiving the honor of "Honorary Fellow" from Tel-Aviv University (frames 38-39).], Dec 12, 1969 (Box 10, Item 12301)
  - Lecture, Jan 5, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12313)
  - Talking Typewriter Brooklyn, Jan 7, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12315)
  - Art Exhibit, Jan 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12318)
  - Ed. Forum, Feb 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12382)
  - Canadian Teachers at US Art Club, Feb 11, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12391)
  - Educational Forum NCCAP, Feb 16, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12396)
  - Para-Professionals Check Repro[duction], Mar 2, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12419)
  - Ed. Forum, May 27, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 12630)
  - Bushwick Display [Appears to be an information fair with different chapters represented and tables with literature on them, including information for students on drug prevention, union literature and information for Para-Professionals.], Jun 15, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12689)
  - Albert Shanker at talking typewriter, Jul 9, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12718)
  - 103rd Precinct Queens, Sep 28, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12779)
  - School Service Officers [Unidentified Individuals], Dec 3, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12938)
  - MES 307 Visitors Wilmington Del, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12998)
  - QuEST Magnetic Tape, Jan 26, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13034)
  - Lecture - Gabe Pressman - Leonard Bukes, Feb 4, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13053)
  - IS 131 Bronx Portable Museum, Feb 16, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13073)
  - Cosmopolitan Orchestra - Carroll Studios, Feb 26, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13105)
  - Lecture JHS & HS, Mar 4, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13121)
  - Planning Map, Mar 10, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13133)
  - JH 60 - Tin cans for recycling & Mr. Possikoft, Mar 15, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13147)
  - Gramercy Park Hotel, Meeting [at the] Explorers[?] Club, Mar 31, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13187)
  - Lecture, Apr 1, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13184)
  - JHS 141 Bronx Symposium on Environment, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13258)
  - Office of Staff Relations Board of Education, May 25, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13353)
  - Exhibit at Grand Central Boy Scout Jamboree, Jun 5, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13371)
  - English / Chinese Language Center, Dec 7, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13712)
  - Filming, Dec 8, 1971 (Box 25, Item 13714)
  - Foreign Language Association, May 17, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14354)
  - Art Exhibit - Prof. Comella BMRC, May 23, 1973 (Box 30, Item 14367)
  - School Children Paintings, May 4, 1976 (Box 30, Item 15191)
- Series XXV: Predecessor Union: Teachers' Guild.
  - Teachers' Guild Hotel Astor [Dewey Luncheon], undated (Box 1, Item 112)
  - Teachers' Guild Dewey Luncheon - Astor, Apr 9, 1949 (Box 30, Item 15589)
  - Teachers' Guild - Dewey Luncheon - Astor Group Shot @ Dais, Apr 9, 1949 (Box 30, Item 15590)
  - Teachers' Guild - Strike, Apr 11, 1949 (Box 30, Item 15587)
  - Teachers' Guild - Strike, Apr 11, 1949 (Box 30, Item 15588)
  - Teachers' Guild [Demonstration calling for cost of living adjustment.], Mar 12, 1950 (Box 1, Item 94)
  - Teachers' Guild (strike), Apr 16, 1950 (Box 1, Item 119)
  - Teachers' Guild [man getting on train], Feb 18, 1952 (Box 1, Item 639)
  - [Charles] Cogen Teachers' Guild [headshots], Dec 5, 1952 (Box 1, Item 812)
  - Teachers' Guild Dinner Hotel Roosevelt, Jan 25, 1953 (Box 1, Item 960)
  - NY Teachers' Guild Mr. [Jeremiah] Bloom [headshots], Feb 12, 1953 (Box 1, Item 941)
  - Teachers' Guild Picketing City Hall [Collection includes corresponding prints.], Apr 14, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1110)
  - Teachers' Guild Group - Sheraton (officers), May 3, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1151)
  - Teachers' Guild Rebecca Dimonson Repro[duction], Sep 22, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1297)
  - Teachers' Guild Teacher's Class CCNY, Nov 7, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1482)
  - Teachers' Guild Hotel Olcott [luncheon], Nov 13, 1953 (Box 1, Item 1492)